Guide to the Watkins Loomis Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series III: Uncataloged Correspondence
  - Lewis, Hilda (Box 58)
  - Lewis, Lloyd (Box 58)
  - Lewis, Sinclair (l942-1954) (Box 58)
  - Lewis, Sinclair (1955-1972) (Box 59)
  - Lewis, Walker (Box 59)
  - Li... (misc) (Box 60)
  - Liddell Hart, Sir Basil Henry (Box 60)
  - Lincoln, Joseph C. (Box 60)
  - Lincoln, Ray (Box 60)
  - Lindsay, Jack (Box 60)
  - Linkletter, C. Monte (Box 60)
  - Lippincott, J.B., Company Publishers (Box 60)
  - Literary Clipping Service (Box 60)
  - Little, Brown and Company Publishers (Box 60)
  - Livesey, Eric M. (Box 60)
  - Livingston, Sir Philip C. (Box 60)
  - Ll - Lo (Misc.) (Box 60)
  - Lobell, William (Box 60)
  - Loeser, Katinka (Mrs Peter DeVries) (Box 60)
  - Lofting, Lynne (Hugh & Josephine Lofting) (Box 60)
  - Long, George (Box 61)
  - Long, John C. (Box 61)
  - Longmans, Green & Co. (Box 61)
  - Looker, Earle (Box 61)
  - Loomis, Katherine Hummel (Katherine Hummel) (Box 61)
  - Lorimer, Jean & Maurice Woodruff "Edith Blair" (Box 61)
  - Lorraine, Marianne Colin Oswald (Box 61)
  - Low, Jacqueline (Box 61)
  - Lubold, Joyce (l960-196l) "Jean Bradford" (Box 61)
  - Lubold, Joyce (1962-1972) (Box 62)
  - Luc - Ly (Misc.) (Box 62)
  - Ludovici, L. James (Box 62)
  - Luff, Terry (Box 62)
  - Lynx, J.J. (Box 62)
  - Maa - MacC (misc.) (Box 63)
  - McAleavy, Henry (Box 63)
  - MacArthur, D. Wilson "David Wilson" (Box 63)
  - McCabe, James (Box 63)
  - McCall's (Box 63)
  - McCann, Hugh Wray (Box 63)
  - McCarthy, Cormac (Box 63)
  - McClellan, Vyonne M. (Box 63)
  - McCormick, Carolyn (Box 63)
  - McCormick, Jay (Box 63)
  - McCormick, Ken (Box 63)
  - McCullers, Carson (Box 64)
  - MacD - MacL (Misc.) (Box 64)
  - McDonald, Hugh (Box 64)
  - McDonald, Jo (Box 64)
  - McDonald, John (Box 64)
  - Macdonald & Co. (Publishers) Ltd. (Box 64)
  - McDowell, Edwin (Box 64)
  - MacDuffie, Marshall: (Box 64)
  - MacGibbon & Kee Ltd General Publishers (Box 64)
  - McGraw-Hill Book Company, Inc. (Box 64)
  - McHale, Tom (Box 64)
  - Mclnerny, Ralph (Box 64)
  - McIntosh, Kenneth (Box 64)
  - McKay Company, Inc. Publishers (Box 64)
  - Mackworth-Praed, Ben & Mike Andrews (Box 64)
  - MacLeod., Alison (Box 64)
  - MacM - Mad (Misc.) (Box 65)
  - The Macmillan Company (Box 65)
  - Maddux, Rachel (l942-1966) (Box 65)
  - Mad.dux, Rachel (1967-1972) (Box 66)
  - Mag - Marq (Misc.) (Box 66)
  - Magnus, Kenneth (Box 66)
  - Maizel, Clarice (Box 66)
  - Malino, Emily (Box 66)
  - Manhattan, Avro (Box 66)
  - Mann, Phillip G. (Box 66)
  - Manning-Sanders, Ruth (Box 66)
  - Manos, Charles (Box 66)
  - Marcus, Geoffrey J. (Box 66)
  - Marion, Jay (Box 66)
  - Markham, Beryl (Box 66)
  - Mars - Mat (Misc.) (Box 67)
  - Marsden, Walter (Box 67)
  - Marshall, Alan (Box 67)
  - Marshall, Bruce (Box 67)
  - Marshall, John (Box 67)
  - Masters, David (Box 67)
  - Matzorkis, Gus (Box 67)
  - Mauldin, Bill (1945-1946) (Box 67)
  - Mauldin, Bill (1947-1949) (Box 68)
  - Mauldin, Bill (1950-1952) (Box 69)
  - Mauldin, Bill (1953-1972) (Box 70)
  - Box 71
  - Max - May (misc) (Box 71)
  - May, Henry John (Box 71)
  - Mayosmith, Margaret (Box 71)
  - Md - Me (misc) (Box 71)
  - Melcher, Harold P., Jr. (Box 71)
  - Merrill, Ethel R. (Box 71)
  - Merriner, Jack H. (Box 71)
  - Merritt, Abraham (Box 71)
  - Meyer, Gordon (Box 71)
  - Meyer, Lucy (Box 71)
  - Mi ... (Misc.) (Box 71)
  - Michelmore, Peter (Box 71)
  - Millar, George Reid (Box 71)
  - Miller, Malcolm (Box 71)
  - Miller, Ralph (Box 71)
  - Miller, Richard "G.B. Greenwood" (Box 71)
  - Millington-Drake, Sir Eugen John Henry Vandersteg (Box 71)
  - Milner, Ronald (Box 71)
  - Minge, Jeanne H. & June U. Taylor (Box 71)
  - Mistral, Gabriela (Lucila Godoy Alcayaga) (Box 71)
  - Mo - Moore (Misc.) (Box 72)
  - Moffett, Cleveland (Box 72)
  - Montgomery, Edward (Box 72)
  - Moore, Samuel Taylor (Box 72)
  - Moorehead, Alan (l942 - 1955) (Box 72)
  - Moorehead, Alan (1956-1963) (Box 73)
  - Moorehead, Alan (1964 - 1972) (Box 74)
  - Moorhead, Lucy Galpin (Box 74)
  - Moos - My (Mjsc.) (Box 74)
  - Moose, Ruth (Box 74)
  - Morgan, Dan & John Kippax (Box 74)
  - Morris, Edita (Box 74)
  - Morrow, William, & Company, Inc. Publishers (Box 74)
  - Morse, Leila Livingston (Box 74)
  - Morse, Roger A. (Box 74)
  - Mosley, Jean Bell (Box 74)
  - Motley, Michael (Box 74)
  - Murdaugh, Lee (Box 74)
  - Mutrux, Robert H. (Box 74)
  - N... (Misc.) (Box 75)
  - Naismith, R.S. (Box 75)
  - Nash, Leila (Leila Nash Cartland) (Box 75)
  - Nathan, Reuben S. (Box 75)
  - National Book Awards (Box 75)
  - Nayman, Anthony (Box 75)
  - Nelson, Diane (Box 75)
  - Nelson, Thomas, & Sons Ltd, Publishers (Box 75)
  - The New American Library of World Literature Inc. (Box 75)
  - Niles, Blair (Box 75)
  - Norton, Olive (Box 75)
  - Norton, W.W., & Company. Inc. Publishers (Box 75)
  - Nowinson, Marie L. (Box 75)
  - O... (Misc.) (Box 75)
  - O'Donnell, James Preston (Box 75)
  - O'Donnell, Mary King (Box 75)
  - Ogilvie, Elizabeth (Box 76)
  - O'Malley, Janet (Box 76)
  - O'Neill, Judith (Box 76)
  - Owen, John E. (Box 76)
  - Owen, Sally (Box 76)
  - Pa... (Misc.) (Box 77)
  - Padfield, Peter (Box 77)
  - Palit, D.K. (Box 77)
  - Palmer, Artis (Box 77)
  - Palmer, Martha (Box 77)
  - Panter-Downes, Mollie Patricia (Box 77)
  - Paramount Pictures Corporation (Box 77)
  - Parker, Robert Allerton (Box 77)
  - Pascal, Ernest (Box 77)
  - Pasto, Tarmo A. (Box 77)
  - Pauley, Barbara (Box 77)
  - Pe - Pl (Misc.) (Box 77)
  - Pearson, Hesketh (Box 77)
  - Pelfrey, William (Box 77)
  - Pepperburg, Roy L. (Box 77)
  - Perceval, Michael "Gerald Bryan", "Hugh Sharpe" (Box 77)
  - Perkins, Faith (Box 77)
  - Perry, Dick (Box 77)
  - Perry, Lilla S. (Box 77)
  - Piccard, Joan R. (Box 77)
  - Pickford, Rhona (Box 77)
  - Pine, William (Box 77)
  - Pinkley, Virgil (Box 77)
  - Playboy (Box 77)
  - Laurence Pollinger Limited Authors' Agents (Box 78)
  - P0 - Py (Misc.) (Box 79)
  - Pollen, Pandora (Box 79)
  - Pollitzer, Anita (Box 79)
  - Pomeroy-Magwood, Pauline (Box 79)
  - Pollock, Robert (Box 79)
  - Poncins, Gontran Jean Pierre de Montaigne, Vicomte de (Box 79)
  - Pook, Peter (Box 79)
  - Poor Henry V. (Box 79)
  - Pound, Arthur (Box 79)
  - Power, Patrick J. (Box 79)
  - Pownall, David (Box 79)
  - Powys, John Cowper (Box 79)
  - Pree, Barry (Box 79)
  - Preston, James (Box 79)
  - Pudney, John (Box 79)
  - G.P. Putnam's Sons Publishers (Box 79)
  - Quant, Mary (Box 79)
  - Ra... (Misc.) (Box 80)
  - Raborg, Frederick (Box 80)
  - Raison, Milton Michael (Box 80)
  - Rambo, Joan (Box 80)
  - Rand, Ayn (Box 80)
  - Random House, Inc. (Box 80)
  - Rappaport, I. Charles (Box 80)
  - Ray, Carleton (Box 80)
  - Ray, Marie Benyon (Box 80)
  - Rayner, Winsome S. (Box 80)
  - Re - Ri (Misc.) (Box 81)
  - The Reader's Digest (Box 81)
  - Reavey, George (Box 81)
  - Redbook Magazine (Box 81)
  - Redding, J. Saunders (Box 81)
  - Reid, Bill (Box 81)
  - Remler, Peter B. (Box 81)
  - Rice, Craig (Box 81)
  - Ringer, Vivian (Box 81)
  - Roberts, Brian (Box 81)
  - Roberts, John (Box 81)
  - Rob... (Misc.) (Box 82)
  - Robins, C. Richard (Box 82)
  - Robinson, Anthony (Box 82)
  - Robinson, Barbara (1960-1965) (Box 82)
  - Robinson, Barbara (1966-1972) (Box 83)
  - Robinson, Virginia (Box 83)
  - Roc - Roo (Box 83)
  - Rodocanachi, Constantinos P. (Box 83)
  - Rohde, Barbara (Box 83)
  - Ronne, Finn (Box 83)
  - Roosevelt, Grace Stackpole Lookwood (Mrs A.B.) (Box 83)
  - Roosevelt, Nicholas (Box 83)
  - Ros - Ry (Misc.) (Box 84)
  - Rosa, Nicholas (Box 84)
  - Rose, Brian (Box 84)
  - Ross, Jonathan (Box 84)
  - Rota, James E. (Box 84)
  - Rothman, Patricia (Box 84)
  - Rowse, Alfred Leslie (Box 84)
  - Rubunstein, Helena (Box 84)
  - Ruddle, Florence (Box 84)
  - Rudo, Rusty (Roslind M. Rudo) (Box 84)
  - Rudolph, William E. (Box 84)
  - Ryan, Cornelius (Box 84)
  - Sa... (Misc.) (Box 84)
  - Saeger, Gregg W. (Box 84)
  - St. Lawrence, Sheila (Box 84)
  - Salk, Jonas E. (Box 84)
  - Salvemini, Gaetano (Box 84)
  - Sandilands, Chiquita (Box 85)
  - Sandrow, Nahma (Box 85)
  - Sandstrom, Flora "Sylvia Sark" (Box 85)
  - Sanford, Cecil L. & Mary Pettis Sanford (Box 85)
  - Sanger, Richard H. (Box 85)
  - Sassoon, Vidal (Box 85)
  - The Saturday Evening Post (Box 85)
  - Saunders, Anne (Box 85)
  - Saunders, Beatrice (Box 85)
  - Saunders, Marion, Authors' & Publishers Representative (Box 85)
  - Saward, Dudley (Box 85)
  - Sayers, Dorothy Leigh (l944-1964) (Box 85)
  - Sayers, Dorothy Leigh (1965-1972) (Box 86)
  - Sc - Se (Misc.). (Box 87)
  - Schmidt, William E. (Box 87)
  - Schreiner, Sam A., Jr. "S.S. Agnew" (Box 87)
  - Scott, Sheila (Box 87)
  - Charles Scribner's Sons Publishers (Box 87)
  - Seabrook, William Buehler (Box 87)
  - Seager, Allan (l943-1947) (Box 87)
  - Seager, Allan (l948-1960) (Box 88)
  - Seager, Allan (1961-1966) (Box 89)
  - Seager, Allan (1967-1972) (Box 90)
  - Seager, Laura A. (Box 90)
  - See, Ingram (Box 90)
  - Seely, Grace Hart (Box 90)
  - Seeman, Bernard (Box 90)
  - Seletz, Jeanette (Box 90)
  - Seiferheld, David F. (Box 90)
  - Senesi, Mauro (Box 90)
  - Serjeant, Richard (Box 90)
  - Seyler, Athene & Steven Haggard (Box 90)
  - Sg - Sh (Misc.) (Box 90)
  - Sharpe, Helen Macy (Box 90)
  - Shaughnessy, Donald F. (Box 90)
  - Shedd, Margaret (Box 90)
  - Sherrill, Dorothy (Box 90)
  - Sherwood, Harriet (Box 90)
  - Short, Christopher C.D. (Box 90)
  - Shutes, Jeanne M. (Jeanne Temenos) (Box 90)
  - Shyer, Marlene Fanta (Box 91)
  - Si - Sl (Misc.) (Box 92)
  - Sidgwick, John (Box 92)
  - Silone, Ignazio (Box 92)
  - Simenon, Georges (Box 92)
  - Simon and Schuster, Inc. Publishers (Box 92)
  - Simpson, Colin (Box 92)
  - Sitwell, (Dame) Edith (Box 92)
  - Sitwell, (Sir) Osbert (Box 92)
  - Sitwell, (Sir) Sacheverell (Box 92)
  - Sitwell lectures (Box 92)
  - Skinner, Susan L. (Box 92)
  - Sm - Sp (Misc.) (Box 93)
  - Smith, Carrietta Parry (Carrietta Parry) (Box 93)
  - Smith, Dorothy Evelyn (Box 93)
  - Smith, Frank (Box 93)
  - Smith, Lola (Box 93)
  - Smith, Martha Ligon (Box 93)
  - Smith, Peter & Peter K. Banks (Box 93)
  - Smith, Thorne (Box 93)
  - Smithford, Kathaleen Rukavina Stevens (Box 93)
  - Snyder, Arthur F.F. (Box 93)
  - Sonneborn, Robert M. (Box 93)
  - Soper, Anthony (Box 93)
  - Sorenson, Charles E. & Samuel T. Williamson (Box 93)
  - Spence, Sylvia (Box 93)
  - Spencer, Magnus (Sir Robert Henry Magnus Spence Saundby) (Box 93)
  - Spencer, Margaret (Box 93)
  - Spender, Jean Maude Henderson (Box 93)
  - Spiro, Merrill Gerber (Merrill Joan Gerber) (Box 93)
  - Sprigge, Elizabeth Miriam Squire (E.S. Napie) (Box 93)
  - Spring, Howard (Box 93)
  - Spunt, Georges (Box 94)
  - Sta - Sti (Misc.) (Box 94)
  - Stace, Jack (Box 94)
  - Stanley, William (Box 94)
  - Starr, Frank C. (Box 94)
  - Stein, Gertrude (Box 94)
  - Stein and Day Publishers (Box 94)
  - Stenstreem, Ruth M. (Box 94)
  - Stephens, Rosemary Carswell (Box 94)
  - Stephensen, P.R. (Box 94)
  - Stern, Henry Root (Box 94)
  - Stevens, James Hay (Box 94)
  - Stewart, Leone (Box 94)
  - Box 95
  - Sto - Sv (misc.) (Box 95)
  - Stokes, Leslie & Sewell (Box 95)
  - Stokoe, E.G. (Box 95)
  - Stone, Erika (Box 95)
  - Stone, Phil & Virginia Swain Strong (Box 95)
  - Stooksbury, Lois (Box 95)
  - Strabel, Thelma (Thelma Strabel Godwin) (Box 95)
  - Straight, John (Box 95)
  - Stringfellow, Olga (Box 95)
  - Strong, Eithne (Box 95)
  - Strong, Kendrick (Box 95)
  - Sullivan Alexander M. (Box 95)
  - Summers, John (Box 95)
  - Sutcliff, Rosemary (Box 95)
  - Sutherland, Douglas (Box 95)
  - Swarthout, Glendon Fred & John Sevacool (1945-1955) (Box 95)
  - Swarthout, Glendon Fred (1956-1960) (Box 96)
  - Swarthout, Glendon Fred (1961-1963) (Box 97)
  - Swarthout, Glendon Fred & Kathryn Blair Vaughn Swarthout (1964-1967) (Box 98)
  - Swarthout, Glendon Fred & Kathryn Blair Vaughn Swarthout (1968-1972) (Box 99)
  - Swi - Sy (misc) (Box 99)
  - Swisher, Viola Hegyi (Box 99)
  - Sykes, Adam & Iain Sproat (Box 99)
  - Ta - Taylor, S. (misc.) (Box 100)
  - Tarrant, Noeline (Box 100)
  - Taylor, F. Sherwood (Box 100)
  - Taylor, Robert C. (Box 100)
  - Taylor, Theodore (1963-1968) (Box 100)
  - Taylor, Theodore (1969-1972) (Box 101)
  - Te... (Misc.) (Box 102)
  - Teague, Walter Dorwin (Box 102)
  - Tec, Nechama (Box 102)
  - Tedlock, E.W., Jr. (Box 102)
  - Terrell, Mark (Box 102)
  - Terres, John K. (Box 102)
  - Tey, Josephine (Elizabeth MacKintosh), "Gordon Daviot" (Box 102)
  - Th... (misc.) (Box 102)
  - Thoby-Marcelin, Philippe & Pierre Marcelin (Box 102)
  - Thomas, Dylan (Box 102)
  - Thomas, Katrina (Box 102)
  - Thompson, Dorothy (Box 102)
  - Thompson, Dunstan (Box 102)
  - Thomson, David (Box 102)
  - Thurlow, Valerie (Box 102)
  - Ti... (misc.) (Box 103)
  - To - Tra (misc.) (Box 103)
  - Toksvig, Signe & Francis Hackett (Box 103)
  - Toledano, Henry (Box 103)
  - Torres, John, Jr. (Box 103)
  - Tranter, John (Box 103)
  - Travers, Pamela L. (1945-1961) (Box 103)
  - Travers, Pamela L. (1962-1972) (Box 104)
  - Tre - Ty (Misc.) (Box 104)
  - Trumbo, Sherry Sonnett (Box 104)
  - Turnbull, Patrick (Box 104)
  - Turner, Florence H. (Box 104)
  - Turner, James (Box 104)
  - Turner, William P. (Box 104)
  - Twombley, Robert (Box 104)
  - Tyler, Poyntz (Box 104)
  - Tymchyshyn, Roman (Box 104)
  - U... (misc) (Box 105)
  - Underwood, Richard A. (Box 105)
  - The University of Chicago (Box 105)
  - Va - Vi (Misc.) (Box 105)
  - Vaizey, John (Box 105)
  - Vance, Guy (J.A. Hughes) (Box 105)
  - Van Deventer, Robert R. (Box 105)
  - Vanider-Hill, Elizabeth (Box 105)
  - Van Wesep, Henry Boeve (Box 105)
  - Verity, Enid & Terence (Box 105)
  - The Viking Press Inc. Publishers (Box 105)
  - Villiers, Alan John (Box 105)
  - Vivante, Arturo (1960-1966) (Box 105)
  - Vivante, Arturo (1967-1972) (Box 106)
  - Von Schilling, James (Box 106)
  - Von Braun, Wernher (Box 106)
  - Von Ulm, Gerith (Box 106)
  - Vorse, Mary Heaton (Box 106)
  - Wa - Wate (Misc.) (Box 106)
  - Wagner, Geoffrey (Box 106)
  - Walker & Company (Box 106)
  - Walpole, (Sir) Hugh Seymour (Box 106)
  - Walton, Donald W. (Box 106)
  - Walton, Francis (Box 106)
  - Walz, Audrey (Box 106)
  - Warner, Eugene P. (Box 106)
  - Washburn, Louise Gurley (Box 106)
  - A. Watkins, Inc.: Ann Watkins (Angeline Whiton Watkins Burlingame) (Box 107)
  - A. Watkins, Inc.: Armitage Watkins (Box 107)
  - Watkins, E. - Wau (Misc.) (Box 108)
  - A.P. Watt & Son Literary agents (Box 108)
  - We... (Misc.) (Box 108)
  - Webster, Benjamin L. (Box 108)
  - Weinman, Rita (Box 108)
  - West, Elizabeth Anne (Box 108)
  - West, John Foster (Box 108)
  - Wharton, Edith Newbold Jones (1942-1972) & Richard Warrington Baldwin Lewis (1965-1980) (Box 108-111)
  - Whe - White, R. (misc.) (Box 111)
  - Wheeler, David (Box 111)
  - White, Ethel Lina (Box 111)
  - White, Terence Hanbury (Box 112)
  - White, Theodore Harold (l946-1953) (Box 112)
  - White, Theodore Harold (1954-1972) (Box 113)
  - Whitehead, Edward & Adinah (Box 114)
  - Whites - Why (Misc.) (Box 114)
  - Wic - Wilk (Misc.) (Box 114)
  - Whitney, Janet Payne (Box 114)
  - Whiton, Augustus Sherrill (Box 114)
  - Whitt, Joseph (Box 114)
  - Whittle, Norah (Box 114)
  - Whyte, Lancelot Law (Box 114)
  - Wic - Wilk (Misc.) (Box 114)
  - Wilkinson, Geoffrey K. (Box 114)
  - Will - Wilt (Misc.) (Box 115)
  - Willeford, Charles (Box 115)
  - Williams, Charles (Box 115)
  - Williams, Elma M. (Box 115)
  - Williams, Terry (Box 115)
  - Willoughby, Amea (Box 115)
  - Willoughby, Ernest (Box 115)
  - Wilson, Beth (Box 115)
  - Wilson, Ruth (Box 115)
  - Wilton, J.A.R. (Box 115)
  - Wim - Wy (Misc.) (Box 116)
  - Winchester, Ellen M. (Box 116)
  - Winnington, Alan (Box 116)
  - Winslow, Eleanor (Box 116)
  - Winton, John (Box 116)
  - Witman, Fred (Box 116)
  - Wolpert, Stanley (Box 116)
  - Wood, Peter (Box 116)
  - Woodruff, Maurice (Box 116)
  - Woolf, Douglas (Box 116)
  - Woolf, Virginia (Box 116)
  - Woon, Basil (Box 116)
  - World Press Photo 1963; ...1964 (Box 116)
  - The World Publishing Company (Box 116)
  - Wraight, Robert (Box 116)
  - Wynn, Wilton (Box 116)
  - X - Z (Misc.) (Box 117)
  - Yeats-Brown, Francis Charles Claypon (Box 117)
  - Yenowich, Matilda (Box 117)
  - Yorke, Susan (Box 117)
  - Young, Francis Brett (Box 117)
  - Young, Gordon (Box 117)
  - Yudkin, John (Box 117)
  - Zang, Francis (Box 117)
- Series IV: Uncataloged Manuscripts, Xerox Copies and Printed Copies
  - Arking, Linda (Box 118)
  - Arlen, Michael (Box 118)
  - Aronson, Theo (Box 118)
  - Aucourt, Joan (Joan Reed), "Joan Phillips" (Box 118)
  - Backus, Jean L. (Box 118)
  - Baldrige, Letitia (Box 118)
  - Baldwin, Raymond P. (Box 118)
  - Bell, Mary Haley (Box 118)
  - Bosworth, James Allan (Box 118)
  - Boyle, Kay (Box 119)
  - Braley, Russell N. (Box 120)
  - Brooke, Edgar D. (Box 120)
  - Bunker, Edward H. (Box 120)
  - Chapman, Leigh (1) (Box 120)
  - Chapman, Leigh (2) (Box 121)
  - Chiba, Milan (Box 121)
  - Cochrane, Shirley Graves (Box 121)
  - Cohen, Leonard (Box 121)
  - Croy, Homer - clippings, 1926 (Box 121)
  - Cooley, John K. (1) (Box 121)
  - Cooley, John K. (2) (Box 122)
  - Dahl, Roald (1) (Box 122)
  - Dahl, Roald (2) (Box 123)
  - Dahl, Roald (3) (Box 124)
  - Dahlstrom, Sture (Box 125)
  - Dammann, Tom & Harle (Box 125)
  - Daves, Jessica (Box 126)
  - Davis, Christopher (Box 126)
  - Davis, Thomas R.A. & Lydia (Box 126)
  - De Fuentes, Patricia (Box 126)
  - De Vries, Peter (Box 126)
  - Dostal, Sudy (Box 126)
  - Du Bois, William Pene (Box 127)
  - Dughi, Nancy (Box 127)
  - Eddy, Roger (Box 127)
  - Fancher, Betsy H. (Box 127)
  - Fernea, Elizabeth Warnock (Box 127)
  - Fussell, Betty (Box 127)
  - Geis, Irving (Box 127)
  - Glaskin, G.M. (Box 127)
  - Graham, Elizabeth (Box 127)
  - Griffith, Valerie Eaton (Box 127)
  - Hamilton, Rosemary (Box 128)
  - Hazleton (Box 128)
  - Honan, Park (Box 128)
  - Horley, Georgina (Box 128)
  - Jefferis, Barbara (Box 128)
  - Jex, Hope Satterthwaite (Box 128)
  - Kotker, Zane (Box 128)
  - Lehmann, John Frederick (Box 128)
  - Loeser, Katinka (Mrs Peter DeVries) (Box 129)
  - Low, Jacqueline (Box 129)
  - Lubold, Joyce "Jean Bradford", "Barbara Robinson" (Box 129)
  - Lundy, Walker & William Schmidt (Box 129)
  - MacArthur, D. Wilson "David Wilson" (1) (Box 129)
  - MacArthur, D. Wilson "David Wilson" (2) (Box 130)
  - McCann, Hugh Wray (Box 130)
  - McCormick, Carolyn (Box 130)
  - Maddux, Rachel (Box 130)
  - Marcus, Geoffrey J. (Box 131)
  - Michelmore, Peter (Box 131)
  - Minoff, Lee (Box 132)
  - Moffett, Cleveland (Box 132)
  - Moorehead., Alan (Box 132)
  - Moose, Ruth (Box 132)
  - Nathan, Reuben S. (Box 132)
  - Nenneman, Richard A. (Box 132)
  - O'Donnell, James Preston (Box 132)
  - Ogilvie, Elizabeth (Box 132)
  - Phelps, Lyon, Raymond Radiguet, & Caresse Crosby (Box 132)
  - Raison, Milton M. (Box 132)
  - Reid, Bill (Box 132)
  - Robinson, Barbara (Box 133)
  - Rohde, Barbara (Box 133)
  - Rosa, Nicholas (Box 133)
  - Rota, James E. (Box 133)
  - Salk, Jonas E. (Box 133)
  - Satter, David (Box 133)
  - Seager, Allan (Box 134)
  - Seager, Laura A. (Box 135)
  - Seaton, George (Box 135)
  - Shedd, Margaret (Box 135)
  - Singer, S. Fred (Box 135)
  - Swarthout, Glendon Fred (Box 135)
  - Taylor, Theodore (1) (Box 135)
  - Taylor, Theodore (2) (Box 136)
  - Taylor, Theodore (3) (Box 137)
  - Thomson, David (Box 137)
  - Trumbo, Sherry Sonnett (Box 137)
  - Tyler, Poyntz (Box 137)
  - Upton, David L. (Box 138)
  - Vivante, Arturo (Box 138)
  - Von Braun, Wernher (Box 138)
  - Wharton, Edith & Richard Warrington Baldwin Lewis (Box 138)
  - White, Theodore Harold (Box 139)
  - Whitehead, Edward (1) (Box 139)
  - Whitehead, Edward (2) (Box 140)
  - Wilkinson, Geoffrey K. (Box 140)
  - Williams, Terry (Box 140)
  - Willoughby, Ernest (Box 140)
  - Wilton, J.A.R. (Box 140)
  - Woolf, Virginia (Box 140)
  - Yorke, Susan (Box 141)
  - Misc. unidentified (Box 141)
- Series V: Uncataloged Contracts and Miscellaneous Documents
  - Abdullah, Achmed (Box 142)
  - Adams, Vyvyan (Box 142)
  - Adkins, Robert F. (Box 142)
  - Amy, Lacey (Box 142)
  - Allen, Dorothy (Box 142)
  - Ankrum, Morris (Box 142)
  - Anthony, Kathatine Susan (Box 142)
  - Anthory, Norman & Belle Livingston (Box 142)
  - Arlen, Michael (Box 142)
  - Armstrong, Margaret (Box 142)
  - Asquith, Lady Cynthia (Box 142)
  - Asquith, Herbert (Box 142)
  - Aswell, James (Box 142)
  - Auger, Helen (Box 142)
  - Babcock, Hayes (Box 142)
  - Badel, A. (Box 142)
  - Banks, Elizabeth (Box 142)
  - Barlow, Samuel Latham Mitchill "Bertrand Huber" (Box 142)
  - Barnett, Joel (Box 142)
  - Barretto, Larry (Laurence Brevoort) (Box 142)
  - Barrie, Sir James Matthew & Lady Cyhthia Asquith (Box 142)
  - Barrows, Edward M. (Box 142)
  - Barry, Richard (Box 142)
  - Bartlett, Vernon (Box 142)
  - Baruch, Dorothy Walter (Box 142)
  - Basch, Ernest (E.B. Ashton) (Box 142)
  - Beahan, Charles (Box 142)
  - Beasley, Mercer (Box 142)
  - Beck, Lily Adams Moresby "E. Barrington", "Louis Moresby" (Box 142)
  - Bedwell, Bettina (Box 142)
  - Beevers, John (Box 142)
  - Bell, Neil (Box 142)
  - Bellah, James Warner (Box 142)
  - Bellamann, Henry (Box 142)
  - Bellamy, Francis Rufus (Box 142)
  - Belloc, Hilaire (Box 142)
  - Benstead, C.R. (Box 142)
  - Bentley, John (Box 142)
  - Berg-Allenberg agency (Box 142)
  - Bertram, Anthony (Box 142)
  - Bezzerides, A.I. (Box 142)
  - Bickel, Mary Dupuy (Box 142)
  - Bierstadt, Edward Hale (Box 142)
  - Birkenhead, Frederick Edwin Smith, 1st Earl of (Box 142)
  - Blake, George (Box 142)
  - Blanton, Ben H (Box 142)
  - Blumenfeld, Simon (Box 142)
  - Bolitho, Hector (Box 143)
  - Bolton, John Robert Glorney (Box 143)
  - Boos, William F. (Box 143)
  - Bottome, Phyllis (Box 143)
  - Boyle, Kay (Box 143)
  - Bradley, Arthur Granville (Box 143)
  - Brady, Nicholas (Box 143)
  - Bramwell, James (Box 143)
  - Brandt, Carl - Brandt & Brandt agency (Box 143)
  - Breckenridge, Gerald (Box 143)
  - Bretherton, Vivien (Box 143)
  - Brice, Mitford (Box 143)
  - Bridges, Constance (Box 143)
  - Brigaud, Armand (Box 143)
  - Bromfield, Louis (Box 143)
  - Bronson, F.W. (Box 143)
  - Brooks, George (Box 143)
  - Brown, Beth (Box 143)
  - Brown, Bob (Robert Carlton Brown) & Rose Brown (Box 143)
  - Brown, Carleton (Box 143)
  - Brown, Lawrence (Roger Delancey) (Box 143)
  - Brown, Zenith "Leslie Ford", "David Frome" (Box 143)
  - Bryant, James McKinley (Box 143)
  - Buchan, John, 1st Baron Tweedsmuir (Box 144)
  - Bundsman, Anton (Box 144)
  - Burgess, R. L. (Box 144)
  - Burlingame, Roger (Box 144)
  - Burnett, Frances Eliza Hodgson (Box 144)
  - Burnett, Whit (Box 144)
  - Bynum, Taylor (Box 144)
  - Callaghan, Morley (Box 144)
  - Campbell, Malcolm (Box 144)
  - Campbell, Ruth Ramsdell (Box 144)
  - Cameron, John (Box 144)
  - Cantwell, Robert (Box 144)
  - Cardozo, Harold (Box 144)
  - Carnevali, Emanuel (Box 144)
  - Carr, John Dickson "Carter Dickson" Microfilm (Box 144)
  - Carson, Robert (Box 144)
  - Carter, E.R. (Box 144)
  - Cartwright, Zack (Box 144)
  - Caspary, Vera (Box 144)
  - Chase, Stuart (Box 145)
  - Church, Richard (Box 145)
  - Churchill, David (Box 145)
  - Clausen, Carl (Box 145)
  - Cleaton, Irene (Box 145)
  - Clements, Eileen Helen (Box 145)
  - Clements, Maie (Maie E. Cohen) (Box 145)
  - Cleugh, James (Box 145)
  - Coffie, Minnie Z. (Box 145)
  - Colby, Nathalie S. (Box 145)
  - Cole, George Douglas Howard & Margaret Isabel Postgate Cole (Box 145)
  - Collier, Basil (Box 145)
  - Collier, Ruth, Inc. agency (Box 145)
  - Collins, Bertrand (Box 145)
  - Collins, Dale (Box 145)
  - Colvin, Ian Duncan (Box 145)
  - Commandini, Adele & Shirley Millard (Box 145)
  - Comptonm Christine & James Monahan (Box 145)
  - Condron, Nina (Box 145)
  - Connor, Rearden (Box 145)
  - Cook, Fannie (Box 145)
  - Cooke, Charles (Box 145)
  - Corbett, Elizabeth & J. Ellis Kirkham (Box 145)
  - Cosgrave, John O'Hara (Box 145)